



aetaylor7@outlook.com



http://ae-taylor.github.io/personal-website/

### **SUMMARY**

As a web developer, I hope to bring my clients' ideas to life. My careers in education and human services have afforded me the opportunity to hone my problem solving and communication skills. Now, I hope to combine these skills with my experience from Rithm School to develop elegant web designs and efficient solutions.



# **ANNA TAYLOR**

## **EXPERIENCE**

# April 2021-Current

Student ● Rithm School: Software Development Bootcamp

#### August 2020-December 2020

Middle School English Teacher • P.L. Dunbar School

#### March 2019-March 2020

Administrative Assistant • Texas Health Care

### September 2017-December 2018

Case Manager/Service Coordinator ● Texas Panhandle Centers

Prior work experience (retail, retail management, childcare) available upon request.

#### **EDUCATION**

# West Texas A&M University, Canyon, TX

- B.A. in Psychology (2015)
- President's List
- Research Assistant in Psychology Lab
- Graduated Magna Cum Laude

### COMMUNICATION

My experience in teaching and case management allowed me to interact with and serve diverse communities. I have experience utilizing feedback to meet the needs of my clients and students.

I communicate complex ideas and solutions in a variety of ways, using appropriate language and terminology for the audience.

I am well-versed in working with a team and enjoy building collaborative and supportive relationships in the workplace.

#### **LEADERSHIP**

I have held management positions in retail environments, and have taken the lead in developing solutions for client satisfaction, such as:

- Current promotion notifications for customers based on customer profile
- Up-to-date pricing lists based on client insurance plan/coverage status

#### **REFERENCES**

Available upon request.